Mss.Ms.Coll.109
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 25.25 linear feet
  - Humane Society of the United States, 1991; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hummeland, Jim, 1995; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H, 1971; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hunkler, Angela F, 1978; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hunt, Edward E, 1959; 1963; 1977; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hunt, Helen, 1980; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hunt, Kevin D, 1993-1994; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Hunt, Morton, 1981; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Huntington, T.W, 1931; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1945; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Huntsman, 1956-1957; 5 items (Box 22)
  - Hurt, Wesley R, 1956; 1958; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Husted, Marjorie Child, 1953; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hutchins, Robert M, 1962-1969; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Huxley, Aldous (Mrs.), 1968-1970; undated; 6 items (Box 22)
  - Huxley, Laura, 1977-1978; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Huxley, Matthew, 1978; 7 items (Box 22)
  - Hyde, H. Montgomery, 1982; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hynes, Samuel, 1983; 1 item (Box 22)
  - H-Misc, 1963-1984; undated; 23 items (Box 22)
  - Iannacone, Sharon M, 1977; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Ingle, Dwight J, 1969; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Ingram, Pamela A.P, undated; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Ingram, T.T.S., 1977; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Irwin, Margaret C, 1978; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Iscovitz, Douglas, 1995; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Isenberg, Carol, 1982; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Isherwood, Margaret, January 17; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Ian, 1990; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Peg, 1982; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Ronald, 1966; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jacob, Teuku MD, 1963; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jacobs, Patricia A, 1961; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jaffe, Russell, 1991; 1992; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jago, John D, 1965; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jameson, M.S, 1956; June 30; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jameson, R.D, 1940-1941; 6 items (Box 23)
  - Jamieson, C. Backer, 1956; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jaynes, Julian, 1979; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jean, Robyn, undated; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jeffcoate, T.N.A, 1961; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jelliffe, D.B, 1985; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jellinek, Roger, 1980; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jenkins, Dorothy, 1978; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jenkins, Gareth, 1990; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jenkins, Phyllis, 1979; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jens, Salome, 1961; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jensen, Arthur, 1973; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jessup, Chad, 1989-1990; undated; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Jett, Michael, 1981; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Joffe, Justin M, 1970-1980; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Joffe, Marcus E, 1939; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Johns, Robert Louis, 1982; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1945-1951; 4 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Ann, 1985; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Brenda J, 1971; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Buffie, 1987-1992; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Charles S, 1945-1946; 7 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Edgar, 1962; 1968; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Edna Ruth, 1993; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Elaine, 1977; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Esther, 1975; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, George, 1984; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Georgia Douglas, 1945; undated; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, J. Chester, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Jan, 1989; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Johnson, John, 1940-1946; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Kevin Orlin, 1993; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Laurence W, 1978; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Robert E, 1972; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jonas, Harold, 1985; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Adam Leroy, 1927; 1928; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jones, Carol, 1978; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, E. Willis, 1970; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, F. Wood, 1943-1948; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Jones, Gary A, 1982; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Jack, 1962; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Jean, 1982; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Marjorie G, 1995; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Mark M, 1968; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jones, Richard D, 1978-1995; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Jones, Richard F, 1940-1941; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Jones, Wood, 1948; 1949; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Jordan, Winthrop D, 1969; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Joslyn, Carl S, 1943; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jourard, Sidney M, 1974; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Joy, Adena, 1978; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Joyce, C.R.B, 1972; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Jubanyik, Raymond J, 1979; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Judd, Elizabeth, 1989; 3 items (Box 23)
  - July, Robert W, 1971; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Junker, Sandra L, 1970; 1 item (Box 23)
  - J-Misc, 1979-1992; 18 items (Box 23)
  - Kachmarik, William, 1981; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1942-1944; 5 items (Box 24)
  - Kagan, Jerome, 1974; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kahler, Alice Loewy, 1957; undated; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Kahn, Carol, 1978; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kallen, Horace M, 1952-1974; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Kallen, Leo A, 1954; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kallir, Jane, 1982; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Kamena, W, 1954; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kanter, B, 1977; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaplan, Arnold R, 1971; 8 items (Box 24)
  - Kaplan, Emanuel B, 1965; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaplan, Gary A, 1991; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Karabin, Nicholas Jr, 1981; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kardiner, Abram, 1946; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Karp, Robert, 1994; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaschube, Dorothea V, 1975; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Katsoff, L.O, 1953-1955; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Kaufer, Waldo, 1939; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kauffer, E. McKnight, 1951; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kauffman, John W, 1961; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaufman, Kelvin S, undated; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kaufman, Sullivan and Jennie, 1958-1998; 19 items (Box 24)
  - Kaufmann, Walter, 1956-1973; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Kawasaki, Mizin P, 1995-1998; 85 items (Box 24)
  - Kean, David W, 1948; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Keddie, Grant, 1989; undated; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Kefauver, Weldon A, 1975; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Keith, Arthur, Sir, 1929-1955; 29 items (Box 24)
  - Keith, Judith, 1969-1991; undated; 11 items (Box 24)
  - Keller, Suzanne, 1992; undated; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Keller, Yvonne, 1989; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kelley, Earl, 1951; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kellog, John G., 1989; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kellogg, Marjorie, 1968; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kellogg's, 1990; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Barbara and Ray, 1978; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Fred, 1939; May 6; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Tom, 1989; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kelman, Norman, 1952; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Kelsey, Linda, 1982-1985; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Kemble, Ted, 1956; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kendig, M., 1951; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kennedy, John A., 1968; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Kennedy, John F. Mrs., 1964; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kennell, John H, 1977-1986; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Kenshalo, Dan R, undated; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kent, Darlene, 1967; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Kephart, C.I, 1963; 1964; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Kepler-May, Ingrid, 1988-1996; undated; 11 items (Box 25)
  - Keppel, David, 1990; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kerner, Fred, 1965;1970; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Kerr, Clark, 1965; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kerr, James W, 1969; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Keynes Geoffrey, 1957; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Khora, Ulen, 1977; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Kilbane, Edward F, 1972; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Killilea, Ann, 1968; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kilpatrick, William H, 1962; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kimmel, Tina, 1988; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, 1989; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Alan F, 1983; 1984; 6 items (Box 25)
  - King, Barbara, undated; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Coretta Scott, 1960; 1978; undated; 4 items (Box 25)
  - King, F, 1981; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, James C, 1979; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, James E, 1978; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Janet Spencer, undated; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Joan, 1977; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Lester S, 1963; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Lori, 1977; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Mary Louise, 1982; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Patrick J, 1978; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Richard, 1980; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Robert T, 1983; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King, Ruth, 1961; 1 item (Box 25)
  - King-Devine, Catherine, 1993; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kinnear, Willis H, 1969; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C, 1948-1953; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kirkendall, Lester A, 1956; 1973-1989; 17 items (Box 25)
  - Kirwan, Celia, 1951; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kisner, Joyce, 1982; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kitch, Michael, 1982; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kitzinger, Sheila, 1974; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Klank, 1971; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Klaus, Marshall H., 1976; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Klein, Ted, 1970; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kleinman, Lou, 1977; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Klepser, K.B, 1972-1976; undated; 11 items (Box 25)
  - Kline, Nathan S, 1969; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Klineberg, Otto, 1950-1990; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde, 1942-1946; undated; 27 items (Box 25)
  - Klug, Brian, 1987-1989; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Klug, I, 1971; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Klug, Sidney and Bertha, 1963-1969; 8 items (Box 25)
  - Knauft, Daniel, 1976; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Knebel, Fletcher, 1974; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Knight, Charles, 1939; undated; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Knobloch, Hilda, 1982; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Knopf, Alfred A, 1960-1983; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Koblak, Dorothy, 1981; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Koenigswald, Ralph, undated; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Koenigswald, V, 1946; 1964; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Koepp, Donald, 1980; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Koerper, Joan, 1979; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kogan, Bernard R, 1986; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kogan, Herman, 1972-1976; undated; 5 items (Box 25)
  - Kohler, Wolfgang, 1942; 1943; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Kolberg, J.H, 1942; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Koldin, Jacqueline, 1944; 1 item (Box 25)
  - Kollstedt, Paula, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 25)
  - Konarzewski, Susan, 1984; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Konner, Melvin J, 1977-1987; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Kophen, Janice, 1989; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Kors, Alan, 1961-1966; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Korzybski, Alfred, 1945-1946; undated; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Koshland, Daniel E, 1991; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kramer, Yetta, 1982; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Krane, Richard V, 1975; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Krassner, Paul, 1961; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kravitz, Harvey, 191971; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kreig, Peggy, 1969; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Krieger, Alen, 1951; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Krinsky, Benjamin, 1978; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Krippner, Stanley, 1987; 1988; undated; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Kroeber, Alfred, 1948; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kroeger, William, 1957; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kroeber, Theodora, 1965-1970; undated; 12 items (Box 26)
  - Krogman, Wilton M, 1938-1953; undated; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Krumblaat, E.B, 1940; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S, 1951-1954; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Kupcinet, Irv, 1971; 1976; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Kupperman, Herbert S, 1967; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kuralt, Charles, 1983-1985; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Kurek, Bruce, 1988; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kurzban, Stan, 1981; undated; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Kuttner, Dr. Robert, 1968; 1 item (Box 26)
  - K-Misc, 1951-1990; 18 items (Box 26)
  - LaBarre, Weston, 1950-1994; 80 items (Box 27)
  - Lachmann, Ismar, 1939; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Lack, David, 1954; 1983; 8 items (Box 27)
    Includes 7 pieces of correspondence between Montagu and Lack, as well as 1 piece from the Sciences magazine, regarding the Montagu-Lack correspondence.
  - Laibow, Rima E, 1985; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Laidler, Harry W, 1961; 1962; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Lambskin, Inc, 1986; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1981; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lampson, Curtis, 1968; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lancaster, Penny, 1982; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Landauer, Michael R, 1975; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lander, Yechiael, 1972; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Landis, James, 1972; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Landor, W.S, June 30; July 30; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Landry, Clorice E, 1955; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Landsman, Harold, 1967; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lane, Suzanne, 1971; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Lange, Thomas V, 1979-1981; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Langer, Ellen, 1982; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Langford, Howard D, 1971; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Langford, Richard E, 1969; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Langham, Ian, 1980; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Langner, Lawrence, 1959-1962; 12 items (Box 27)
  - Langston, Berta, 1970; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lansing, Sherry, 1980; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lapp, Danielle, 1993; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Larry, Elise P, 1969; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Larson, Cecilia, 1977; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Larsson, Raymond, 1957; 1 item (Box 27)
  - La-Rue, Charlotte, 1943; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lasch, Christopher, 1983; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lasker, Gabriel, 1947; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Laskin, Donald Neal, 1972; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lathan, Janet Rhodes, 1972; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Laughlin, William S, 1948-1968; 11 items (Box 27)
  - Laurence, William L, 1959; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lautenberg, Frank R, 1991; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lauter, Paul, 1969; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lavender, Teresa A, 1981; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lawrence, Barbara, 1967; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lawrence, John H, 1965; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lawrence, W.E, 1937; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lawrey, E.J, 1983; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Lawson-Johnston, Frederic, 1929-1930; undated; 9 items (Box 27)
  - Layne, Janet, 1981; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lazar, Irving Paul, 1978; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lazar, Dan, 1970; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Leach, Edmund R, 1966-1982; 11 items (Box 27)
  - Leake, Chauncey, 1944-1977; 45 items (Box 27)
  - Leakey, Louis, 1947-1959; 6 items (Box 27)
  - Leakey, Richard E, 1975; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Lean, Tangye, 1959; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Leavitt, Elizabeth Lynne, 1979-1980; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Lebensohn, Zigmond M, 1967; 1 item (Box 27)
  - LeBoyer, F, 1976; undated; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Lederer, Eppie (Landers, Ann), 1950; undated; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Lee, Mary Douglas, 1952; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lee, Paul, undated; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lee, Richard, 1981; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lee, Rick, 1995; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lee, Robert A, 1980-1984; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Lee, Robert J, September 18; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leeds, Helen, 1967; 1968; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Legman, G, 1953-1977; undated; 9 items (Box 28)
  - Lehmann, Hermann, 1959; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Leibmann-Smith, Richard, 1985; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Leibowitz, Ruth Q, 1986; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leighton, Mary S, 1981; 2 items (Box 28)
  - LeMaine, G, 1977; 1 item (Box 28)
  - LeMay, Harding, 1965; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lenhart, Charmenz S, 1978; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lennox, B., 1961; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lentz, Theodore F, 1955; 1958; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Leo, Pam, 1997; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leonard, George, 1978; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leonard, Gini, 1964; undated; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Leonard, John, 1970; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lerner, Max, 1956-1957; undated; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Le-Rouzic, Jacq, 1957; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lervold, Linda, 1970; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leshan, Eda J, 1986; 1987; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Leslie, Shane, 1958; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leslie, Susan, 1984; 1985; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Lessa, W.A, 1953; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lesser, Alexander, 1939-1982; undated; 22 items (Box 28)
  - Lester-Massman, Gordon, 1982; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Leurs, Herb, 1995; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levin, Joan, 1994; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levene, George, 1947; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levine, Arnold, 1987-1990; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Levine, Howard, 1960; February 4; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Levine, Jon, 1982; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levine, Philip, May 25; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levins, Dick, 1959; undated; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1965; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Levitan, Max, 1959-1989; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Levy, Constance and Ben, 1948-1956; undated; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Levy, Harriet, 1972; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lewin, Roger, 1983-1987; 11 items (Box 28)
  - LeWinter, Oswald, undated; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lewis, Anthony, 1988; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Lewis, E.G, 1969; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lewis, Lisa J, 1981; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lewis, Michael, 1992; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lewontin, R.C, 1974-1984; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Lewry, Dawn V, 1977; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Library of Congress, 1943; 1969; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lichty, Phoebe, 1997; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lieberman, Dan, 1978; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lieberman, Leonard, 1983-1996; undated; 73 items (Box 30)
  - Liebers, The, 1955; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Liedloff, Jean, 1991; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lief, Harold I, 1963; 1968; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Light the Quarterly of Light Verse, 1991; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lightcap, Beatrice, 1965; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lilly, Elizabeth, 1963; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lilly, John C, 1963; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Linden, Millicent, 1982; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lindley, Frances, 1977; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lindner, Robert, 1952; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lindsay, June McKee, 1975-1982; undated; 8 items (Box 29)
  - Link, Jan, 1984; undated; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Linkroum, Richard, 1969; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Linnell, Mildred, 1981; 1 item (Box 29)
  - LInnet, Catherine, 1980; 1981; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lintemuthe, Pat, 1982; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Linton, Ralph, 1938-1951; 7 items (Box 29)
  - Lipman, Betty, 1962; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lippitz, Charles A, 1971; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lipschutz, Alejandro, 1947; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lipschutz, Isabelle Gardner, 1968; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Little, Kenneth, 1948-1974; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Little, Michael A, 1995; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Littlewood, Hardy, 1984; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lively, Mary Ann, 1969; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Livingston, Lyn, 1974; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Livingstone, Frank B, 1963; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Locke, Louis G, 1959; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lockhart, Jean D, 1976; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Loewy, H.M, 1985; undated; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Loewy, Lilly, 1964; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Loewy, Nancy Jane, 1992; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lomax, Alan, 1970; July 20; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Long, Beverly Whitaker, 1982; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Long, Herman, 1952; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Long, Perrin H, 1962-1963; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Loomis, Robert, 1972; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lopez, M.W, 1947-1964; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Lopez, Thomas F, 1969; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lorena, Mary, 1987; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lottinville, Savoie, 1966; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Loudon, John, 1988; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Loure, Alice, undated; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Loveridge, A, 1938; 1944; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lovejoy, Arthur O, 1955; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lowen, Alexander, 1970; 1974; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lowen, Jeannette, 1986-1995; 6 items (Box 29)
  - Loye, David, 1968-1998; undated; 17 items (Box 29)
  - Lucas, Bob, 1993; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lucas, F.A, 1928; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1971; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Luce, Gay, 1977; 1979; undated; 6 items (Box 29)
  - Ludwig, R.M, 1982; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Luria, S.E, 1974; undated; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lunde, Anders S, 1971; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lynch, James, 1981; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lynch, Rosonita, 1981; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lyons, Andy and Harriet, 1989-1990; undated; 8 items (Box 29)
  - Lyons, Kevin J, 1984; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lyttle, Bradford, 1972; 1 item (Box 29)
  - L-Misc, 1952-1990; 20 items (Box 29)
  - Maag, Paul, 1968; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Mabee, Carleton, 1979; 1984; 3 items (Box 31)
  - Mabon, John Scott, 1969; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McAllister, R.G, 1996; 1 item (Box 31)
  - MacAvoy, 1965; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McBride, Mary Margaret, 1942; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCabe, Marla and Jim, 1965-1990; 6 items (Box 31)
  - McCain, J.W, 1939; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCall, W.A, 1939; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCarthy, Catherine, 1950; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCauley, Marianne, 1977; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McClain, Donna H, 1985; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCleary, Fiona, 1939-1990; undated; 8 items (Box 31)
  - McClintock, Lillian, 1974; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McClung, Karen L, 1972; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McClure, Diana L, 1979; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McColley, Grant, 1938-1941; 3 items (Box 31)
  - McConnell, Joan, 1984; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCormick, Ken, 1963-1986; 12 items (Box 31)
  - McCowen, Joan, 1989; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCoy, Robert B, 1977; 3 items (Box 31)
  - McCoy, Tom, 1972; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McCrie, Robert, 1975; 1977; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McCulloch, Warren S, 1959; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McDaniel, W.B, 1966; 1973; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McDonald, Audrey, 1982; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McDonald, Worden, 1982; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McDongall, W, 1931; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McDougall, Sharon, 1977; 1 item (Box 31)
  - MacDonald, Dwight, 1967;1973; October 1; June 25; June 10; 6 items (Box 31)
  - MacFarlan, Carol, 1988; 1 item (Box 31)
  - MacFarlane, Jill, March 3; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McGinnis, Agnes, 1981; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Macgowen, Edna and Kenneth, 1951-1975; March 9; December 20; 60 items (Box 31)
  - MacGowen, Joan, 1977; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McGrath, Alice, 1976; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McGrath, Patricia, 1994; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McGregor, J.H, 1943-1954; 5 items (Box 31)
  - McKay, Susan, 1979; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McKee, June, 1978; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McKelvey, Raymond G, 1963; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McKeown, T., 1961; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McKinney, Betsy, 1977; 3 items (Box 31)
  - McKinnon, Alastair, 1954; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McKusick, Victor A, 1964; 1968; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McLaren, Bob, 1980; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McLaine, Shirley, 1968-1984; 6 items (Box 31)
  - McLaughlin, Jody, 1987; 1989; 2 items (Box 31)
  - MacLean, Charles, 1980; 1 item (Box 31)
  - MacLean, Paul D, 1973; 1974; 3 items (Box 31)
  - McCovern, George, 1967; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McLeod, Mike, 1980; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McLuhan, Marshall, 1956-1972; undated; 38 items (Box 31)
  - McMahon, J.H.G, 1970; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McMahon, Peggy O'Mara, undated; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McNamee, Gregory, 1987; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Macrae, Elliot B, 1944; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Macrae, John, 1977; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McWilliams, Carey, 1945-1965; 3 items (Box 31)
  - Macy, George, 1969; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Magar, Magar E, 1972; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Magee, Bryan, undated; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Mahlaw, Marilaise, 1983; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Mahn, Elaine S, 1977; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Maisel, Edward, 1989; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Majno, Guido, 1984-1995; 13 items (Box 32)
  - Makara, Frank, 1981; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Malinowski, Bronislaw, 1933-1941; 24 items (Box 32)
  - Malloch, Archibald, 1939; 1940; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Malsbury, Susan, 1998; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mandelbaum, David G, 1955-1967; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Manheim, Jerome H, 1981; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mann, Donald, 1977; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mann, Laurie, 1981; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mann, Martin, 1966; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mann, O.G, 1983; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mansbridge, Bruce, 1982; 1984; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mansbridge, Jane, 1981; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mansbridge, Ronald and Georgia, 1942-1997; 24 items (Box 32)
  - Manson, J.D, 1966; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Manson, William C, 1993; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marcus, David A, 1971; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marcus, George E, 1983; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Marcus, Stanley, 1965-1996; 8 items (Box 32)
  - Marg, P, 1951; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1952; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Marie, Janet, undated; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Mariola, Joe, 1982; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mark, Vernon H, 1971-1972; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Markey, T.L, 1982; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marks, Jonathan, 1993-1998; 23 items (Box 32)
  - Marler, Joan, 1988; 1993; 1996; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Marmion, Bridget, 1981; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marmor, Judd, 1955-1968; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Marshack, Alexander, 1974; undated; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Marshall, Lawrence Kennedy, 1977; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marshall, John David, 1974; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Marshall, Robert J, 1981; 1994; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Marston, A, 1948; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Martin, Calvin, 1991; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Martin, James, 1962-1964; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Martindell, Anne, 1973; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marton, Mort N, 1982; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marton, Pier, 1988; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Marx, Louis, 1957; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Maslow, A.H, 1952-1968; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Mason, J. Alden, 1961; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Masserman, Jules, 1963; 1972; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Masters, Roger D, September 11; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mastrude, R.G, 1950; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Masuga, Clara, 1985; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Matthews, Frances, 1982; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Matthews, Robert W, undated; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Matthies, Judith K, 1976; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mattutat, Edward John, 1982; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mauners, Bob, 1974; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Maxson, Stephen, 1974; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Maxwell, Richard, undated; 1 item (Box 32)